The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
♪ Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano ♪
The dreams I see are my secret
♪ Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano ♪
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
♪ Akai manto hira hira ♪
A red cape fluttering
♪ Uma o tobasu oujo ♪
Galloping on a horse—the princess
♪ Sore ga atashi ♪
That’s me!
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Ribon no kishi wa ♪
The Knight of the Ribbon,
♪ Honto wa hontto wa ♪
Truly, truly,
♪ Atashi nano sa ♪
It’s really me!
Twenty-First Episode
The Magic Cookies
The World's Best Snack
All right, it's time to wake Lord Sapphire.
Lord Sapphire, it is time.
Lord Sapphire, it's time to go to the secret room.
Yeah, I know.
I'll be right back.
You must not.
Please study properly until nine o'clock.
You're late today.
Now, hurry and change.
Allow me to help you.
Here is your dress.
Is this it?
The one Mother made for me?
Yes, it is.
You must study cooking and sewing so you won't be outdone by any queen.
But if I wear women's clothes, I can't ride my horse!
If you act like a proper girl, I'm sure you'll grow to like it.
Come on now, please change.
I told you, I'll do it myself!
Stop nagging me!
Come now.
My, how adorable!
Now first, slice this bread.
Okay.
Huh? It won't cut.
When that happens, warming the knife helps it cut easily.
Look, like this.
Slice, slice, chop...
This isn't working.
It won't cut right.
Hey, do you have a longer knife?
We have something like this, but...
Yeah, this will do.
That's used for preparing fish.
What are you doing?
There! Here we go!
Slice, slice, slice, slice!
Wow, this cuts way better!
Ah, no, you can't! When you cook, you have to follow proper cooking rules!
Okay.
Good morning, everyone. Oh my...
Good morning.
You certainly slept in late.
Who is that girl?
Why, if it isn't Sapphire!
Here's breakfast!
Well, isn't that thoughtful of you?
Here you go, Father.
And this is for Mother.
Hmm, when she acts like this, she really is a girl after all.
See? I can do it if I try.
Huh? What's wrong? Why'd you make that weird sound?
Oh, nothing, it's just...
What a sight...
And after I took the trouble to set it so nicely!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Could someone put a tablecloth over it?
Oh, uh, this...
I'm sorry, Father.
Never mind that, just hurry up, Sapphire.
Hey, wait a minute.
You really do seem better off as a boy.
What? Nothing at all?
Well, actually...
Is that true?
It's these biscuits.
Handstand!
Flip!
Bark!
I put a new potion I made into these biscuits—
one that makes people do whatever they're told.
Good. Have them make plenty of those biscuits.
And I'll feed it to the King, Queen, and Sapphire at snack time today.
That was delicious.
Hey, why did you eat my precious biscuit?
Biscuits that make you do as you're told.
Hey, where are you going, you parrot? Wait!
It's time to become a boy.
It's finally time.
All right, off I go!
Goodness, perhaps I raised her too much like a boy.
What am I going to do with her?
Stop!
It's a parrot.
How strange.
Here, perch on my hand.
This is Nylon's pet parrot.
Hey, parrot!
Prince Sapphire!
Nylon, this is yours, right?
Here you go.
N-No, that won't be necessary.
Let's go for a ride later.
That's odd.
I wonder what's wrong with this parrot.
Hey, if you know something, tell me.
Eat a biscuit.
If you eat it?
Make biscuits.
Make biscuits?
Hey, what kind of biscuits?
Duralumin!
This parrot was talking about biscuits laced with an obedience drug!
Biscuits laced with an obedience drug? What on earth is that?
Nylon, do you know something about this?
I have no idea what you mean. I'm completely...
That's a lie!
You looked like you knew a moment ago!
What on earth is wrong with you?
You must have had a terrible dream last night.
Those biscuits are definitely for some evil plot.
If they're biscuits, they must be having a sweet shop make them.
All right, I'm definitely going to find them.
You're Prince Sapphire, right?
Where are you going?
There's a pastry shop in the woods! I'm going to go look for it!
This is all sponge cake! The snow on the roof is whipped cream.
How cute.
The popcorn gravel sure is delicious.
Wow, it's tasty!
Hey!
What do you want here?!
Kids who just come to gawk and eat should go home!
I'm busy making a huge biscuit order!
The biscuit order...
So he really is making them here.
What should I do?
Ah, I know!
Opal!
Go to the castle and fetch me a girl's dress!
Great, this will do.
Now Opal, wait here!
Who is it, when I'm so busy?!
Oh, a customer?
No, I'm looking for work.
I heard the baker here is a kind person who would surely hire me.
Um, do you have any work for me?
Well, I'm slammed today, so you're hired!
Yay! I'm so happy!
Wait, do you make sweets in a small space like this?
Don't be foolish!
How could I bake cakes in a shop like this?!
Wow, you have a room in the basement too!
What an amazing workshop!
It's magnificent!
After all, I'm the greatest baker in the world!
Sapphire!
Yes!
Light the fire in the furthest stove!
Okay!
Just set it on fire? That's easy!
Well, well, Sapphire. Don't you even know how to start a fire?
I'm sorry, the wood is damp...
Sapphire, look!
Everything's pitch black!
Even the biscuit ingredients are pitch black!
So you won't make any more biscuits?
Don't be ridiculous!
I'll finish it by snack time today!
Clean up!
Yes!
Alright. Now to add the medicine they ordered...
Now, you're going to help me.
First, you quickly take the dough,
pat it down like this, and make it about this size.
Then you bake it later.
Pat, pat... Huh?
It's huge!
Oh, no!
Mine fell apart!
Enough! Put the ones I made into the oven!
Okay!
I know!
I'll mess up on purpose and ruin these biscuits!
You fool!
How could you be so careless?!
I'm sorry, Mr. Cookie!
I'm so clumsy...
Why can't you handle such a simple task?
Even a baby could do this!
Can't you act like a proper girl?
Old man, you in here?
Old man!
Is our order ready?
I'm baking them right now!
You'll have to wait a little longer!
Who's that girl?
She's my assistant.
Right, fresh out of the oven!
Help me out!
Yes!
Very good!
We'll take the cookies!
By the way, what medicine did you put in these sweets?
It isn't poison, is it?
Don't be ridiculous!
It's a supplement called Vitamin C!
A supplement... Could it be...?
Girl!
Why did you just say "could it be"?
You know something about these biscuits, don't you?
N-N-No, I don't know a thing!
Nothing about any medicine...
These are just delicious biscuits!
Is that so?
Then you can eat one of these biscuits!
They're just biscuits with Vitamin C, right?
Go on, try it!
Eat it!
Come on, eat up!
Go on, eat!
Try a bite!
All right!
It's true!
She knows about the biscuits!
Was it bitter?
Hold this!
Opal!
Let's go!
Wait!
Come on!
Quick, run!
She getting away!
Help!
Who ordered those biscuits made?!
Those poisoned biscuits!
Speak!
Alright, so you won't talk.
Fine, you don't have to!
I'll take those biscuits!
Out of my way!
I'm saved!
Mr. Cookie!
Please give me those biscuits!
Oh, Your Highness!
N-No, I can't!
These biscuits are for the person who ordered them!
I'm supposed to get them!
Please!
No, absolutely not!
I can't hand these over!
What's wrong?
Lord Nylon, it failed.
It failed?
Weren't the poisoned biscuits ready?
What?
Prince Sapphire showed up?
Damn it!
All right!
May I help you?
I'll handle Sapphire.
In the meantime, go back and get the biscuits!
You guys!
Take care of Sapphire!
Go!
Good grief!
Looks cool, doesn't it?
Hello?
Pardon me.
You again!
Villains!
Got 'em!
Good work!
I leave the rest to you!
Don't shoot!
I'm Cookie!
No, don't shoot!
Why are you shooting?!
We can't have you blabbing about making poisoned biscuits.
So you'll have to die!
Damn it!
So that's it!
I was tricked!
Your Highness, I didn't know that medicine was poison.
That's why I did as they said and made poisoned treats.
Do you know who they're going to feed those poisoned biscuits to?
Yes, I do.
To everyone in the castle.
The King, the Queen, the Prince, and... oh no!
I forgot something terrible!
Those biscuits were meant to be today's snack!
Today's snack?
Oh no!
It's almost snack time!
Ah!
There's still one left over there!
That's it!
If we make them eat this biscuit, they'll obey us just like the Queen Mother!
All right!
Take this!
Ouch!
Listen up, whoever ate the biscuit!
You don't need to capture me anymore!
Yes, sir!
See? The potion in the biscuit works!
Your Highness, we won't stand in your way anymore!
Now, tell me who ordered you to defeat me!
I don't know their name.
I was only asked by the soldiers...
Don't the others know?
Your Grace, quickly, to the castle!
Oh, right!
Now, all of you, go home!
Never come to this forest again!
Nylon, do they taste good?!
Of course they do!
I had Silverland's finest baker make them!
All right, give this to the castle cook at once...
...and make everyone who sides with Sapphire eat it!
Yes, sir!
And did you get rid of the person who made the biscuits?
They're taking care of them along with Sapphire right now.
What, Sapphire too?!
Are you sure about this? Sapphire is a skilled fighter!
I'm certain it'll be fine, but... let's take one more precaution.
Tank squad, tank squad, come in!
This is a secret order from Lord Duralumin!
This potion made that violent beast docile in an instant...
If Father and Mother eat it, they'll be at Lord Duralumin's mercy...
Then...
Your Majesty, it's time for your snack.
Put it on that table over there.
Could you go call everyone else?
We can eat together.
Yes.
It's a tank!
Hurry!
Here goes!
Stop!
Stop, or I'll cut you down!
Who ordered you to attack me?
I was just following the captain's orders...
Liar!
Duralumin or Nylon gave the order, didn't they?
I don't know!
Opal!
Just dump them somewhere!
You guys walk back!
Yes.
Are they still not here?
They'll be right here. Please, go ahead and eat.
No, no, let's eat together.
These biscuits look delicious.
Sorry we're late, Your Majesty.
You kept me waiting.
You're always late.
Prince Sapphire has returned!
Open the gate!
Hurry up and open it!
What are you doing?!
My, these biscuits look delicious.
If only Sapphire could bake biscuits like these...
I'm sure Lady Sapphire will learn how to someday.
Sapphire!
What on earth happened?!
Mother, Father.
Next time, I'll bake delicious biscuits for you!
Oh, my...
What happened, Sapphire?
Tell me about it.
Okay.
But without proof, we don't know who had those biscuits made.
What is it?!
Sapphire used the biscuits to turn our men to her side!
You fools!
Oh, my...
They're a bit burnt, but Mr. Cookie taught me.
They're tasty! Huh?
Hey, these are actually pretty good.
They really are.
Pretty good for your first try.
Of course they are!
Because I made them!
So bitter!
Darn it!
Sapphire, you can do things girls do just fine.
With some effort, you could even bake the world's best cake.
Yeah!
I'll get better, Father. You'll see.
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen ♪
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
♪ Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen ♪
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
♪ Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo ♪
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
♪ tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai ♪
Our bonded hearts will never part.
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP